Life is full of choices, some inconsequential, some really significant.
生活中充满了选择，有些无关紧要，有些则至关重要。
But sometimes it can be hard to make the correct one.
但有时，做出正确的选择可能很难。
What are the obstacles that stand between us and a good outcome?
那么，阻碍我们获得良好结果的障碍是什么呢？
Some of us just find it hard to decide.
我们中的一些人就是觉得难以做决定。
Alice Boyes, writing for Harvard Business Review, tells us this can be connected to perfectionism, where people attempt to find a perfect solution to any problem and are unable to move forward when they can't find one.
爱丽丝·博伊斯在为《哈佛商业评论》撰写的文章中告诉我们，这可能与完美主义有关，即人们试图为任何问题找到完美的解决方案，而当找不到时便无法继续前进。
It might seem that being indecisive would stop us making the right decision, but in fact it could actually help us make the correct ones.
看起来犹豫不决似乎会阻止我们做出正确的决定，但实际上，它可能反而有助于我们做出正确的选择。
Susan Krauss in Psychology Today reminds us that people often make bad decisions because they base them on preconceptions rather than the context in which things happen.
苏珊·克劳斯在《今日心理学》中提醒我们，人们常常做出糟糕的决定，是因为他们基于先入为主的观念，而非事情发生的具体背景。
She highlights a paper by researcher Iris Schneider which finds that indecisive people are more likely to look at different perspectives and use them to come to a better decision.
她重点提到了研究员艾里斯·施奈德的一篇论文，该论文发现犹豫不决的人更有可能审视不同的视角，并利用这些视角来做出更好的决定。
So, it could be that a more significant barrier to making the best choice is our cognitive biases.
因此，阻碍我们做出最佳选择的更大障碍，或许是我们自身的认知偏见。
David Robson, speaking to the BBC's Crowd Science, tells us that intelligence can sometimes stop people making the right decision.
大卫·罗布森在接受BBC《众科学》节目采访时表示，聪明有时反而会阻碍人们做出正确的决定。
People sometimes use intelligence to invent justifications for irrational beliefs.
人们有时会利用才智为不合理的信念编造理由。
He believes that humility is key to making a good decision.
他认为，谦逊是做出正确决定的关键。
People who can accept that they might be wrong are more likely to consider different viewpoints.
能够接受自己可能犯错的人，更有可能考虑不同的观点。
He is backed up on this by Jeff Bezos.
杰夫·贝索斯也支持这一观点。
Tech CEO Jason Fried recalls the Amazon founder saying how the people who were right a lot of the time were the people who often changed their minds.
科技公司首席执行官贾森·弗里德回忆道，这位亚马逊创始人曾说过，那些经常正确的人，往往是那些经常改变想法的人。
So, maybe rather than indecision, it might be intelligence and decisiveness, backed up by our biases that actually stop us making good choices.
因此，或许阻碍我们做出正确选择的并非犹豫不决，反而是被我们的偏见所支撑的智慧和果断。
While humility and indecisiveness could help us pick the best option.
而谦逊和犹豫不决则可能帮助我们选出最佳选项。